<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Increase your revenues using sales program and artificial intelligence technologies]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Increase your revenues using sales program and artificial intelligence technologies]]></description>
        <link>http://accessgroup.help/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2017 16:28:49 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://accessgroup.help/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2017 16:28:48 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[WHAT OUR CUSTOMERS SAY]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1><strong>WHAT OUR CUSTOMERS SAY</strong></h1>,<blockquote>&ldquo; Their passion, energy and commitment to innovation are inspirational. They are innovators when it comes to getting diverse groups of people together to improve various innovations on the global stage.&quot;&mdash; Ross Pellizzari, Managing Director, Avaya</blockquote>]]></description>
            <link>http://accessgroup.help/what-our-customers-say/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">7ffa3816-e284-4baa-b470-a20c7d1fe10c</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 14 Jan 2017 03:19:39 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[List of Lead Generation Technologies & Free Resources]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>List of Lead Generation Technologies &amp; Free Resources</h1>,<h2>LeadCrunch</h2>,<a href="http://promo.leadcrunch.com/taimour" data-role="cta">Leverage AI to Get New Leads</a>,<p><a href="http://promo.leadcrunch.com/taimour" title="">We add “artificial intelligence” into your sales campaigns to instantly identify qualified leads. Compare our results to any of your existing sales campaigns and you will quickly find higher and more profitable sales volumes at a much faster rate.</a></p>]]></description>
            <link>http://accessgroup.help/game-changing-lead-generation-technologies-coaching-and-fre/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f972a213-d9ff-4683-88e3-973556a1e66a</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 03:02:03 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Webinars & Events]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Webinars &amp; Events</h1>,<h2>How to Reduce the Time Sales Reps Spend on Non Selling Activities?</h2>,<p>On August 11th, join me and Taimour Zaman on an amazing webinar titled: "How to Reduce the Time Sales Reps Spend on Non Selling Activities?"</p>,<p>You will leave the session with:</p>,<ul><li>How to structure communications and technologies to reduce non selling activities?</li><li>Meet Adrian and understand why he’s one of the most successful executive sales coaches.</li><li>An opportunity to meet and network with peers from across North America.The session will be from 12:00 pm EST to 1:00 pm EST and there are limited seats available. Please RSVP right away.</li></ul>,<p><a href="http://https/access-group.clickfunnels.com/webinar-registration7yqodb29">https://access-group.clickfunnels.com/webinar-registration7yqodb29</a></p>]]></description>
            <link>http://accessgroup.help/webinars-and-events/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ac9c5b76-9939-4333-88ef-fbc6224c8d8b</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 21:23:25 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Blog]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1><strong>Blog</strong></h1>,<h2><strong>How to get 350 qualified B2B leads in less than 71 hours?</strong></h2>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/a8faf00a-55fb-4267-8473-1f501c0fbb2e.jpg">,<p>Have you ever felt frustrated going through junk leads? I know I have.</p>,<p>Going through junk leads (people who are not interested in your product/service) is time consuming, costly and energy draining.</p>,<p>Most organizations that I know, have high sales quotas and must go through a lot of junk leads in order to meet their quarterly sales goals.</p>,<p>As a senior lead generation consultant &amp; coach, I’ve brought in hundreds of millions of dollars into companies like Adobe, Microsoft, IBM, CapGemini, Deloitte, Cisco Systems, Siemens and fast companies similar to yours.</p>,<p>From my experience, I can tell you for sales people to meet their quota, they need to have 3-5 times their quota in in their pipeline. Said differently, if a sales person’s quota is $100 million for this quarter, that sales person will need to have $300 million - $500 million in their pipeline.</p>,<p>So, if I want to meet my sales quota every, I need qualified leads. If I need qualified leads, I need to go through a lot of junk leads so that I can find my qualified leads. Said differently, meeting my quota = going through a lot of junk leads. If you consistently want to meet your sales quota, you consistently have to go through you a lot of junk leads.</p>,<p>Here comes the best part:</p>,<p>1) Quotas keep getting bigger – which means the volume of junk leads I have to go through becomes bigger.</p>,<p>2) Sales people are inherently lazy. And,</p>,<p>3) Sales cycles are getting longer and customers have far more alternative options than they did compared to 20 years ago.</p>,<p>In short, the time and frustrations in dealing with junk leads seems to be exponentially increasing, and if we want to see increase revenues, reduce sales cycle times, or simply have the ability to attract and retain the best sales people, then we have to fix the junk lead issue. Period.</p>,<p>The problem as I see is that there are a lot of junk leads that get into the organizations through:</p>,<ul><li>Websites,</li><li>Social media,</li><li>Cold calling,</li><li>Buying lists or whatever other way people generate leads,</li><li>Useless and not engaged channel partners, and</li><li>Hiring the wrong sales people</li></ul>,<p>This reminds me of my story in how I was introduced to artificial intelligence lead generation technologies and how it changed our entire organization as well as our client companies.</p>,<p>I first got a call by the CEO of an artificial intelligence lead generation company who was pitching his technology to me.</p>,<p>Right from the start, we had a few issues to deal with.</p>,<p>The first problem was me.</p>,<ul><li>I’m skeptic kinda guy. I don’t have time to waste and given my day to day job, I feel like I know it all. Just so you know, I test 7-10 lead generation systems, technologies, etc. every week.</li></ul>,<ol><li>Name a lead generation technology (Growbots, Hubspot, lead gibbons, woodpecker, etc.) or a lead generation system (eRational marketing, Dan Kennedy’s product launch formula, etc.) I’ve tested them, reported the results and have a good understanding of which technologies and sales programs are best suited for different organizations.</li><li>The next problem is this thing called lead generation artificial intelligence sounds like running “analytics” on my customer data and calling it something else – like artificial intelligence. Oh, by the way, I’ve tested a few sales analytics software solutions and they are a hit or miss. So I’m not sure repacking something that I already know about is something would work for me.</li></ol>,<p>Our next problem was that we already have various systems in place.</p>,<p>Surely none of the technologies we use is perfect. But each technology or sales program produces some kind of a unique value. It’s like having your company on Twitter and on LinkedIn. 2 different platforms and if you know how to use them, you will get 2 different kinds of results. But, by the end of the day, you have to keep 2 different platforms that don’t talk nor connect with each other. In the context of our independent lead generation technologies, one of our systems requires traffic. Another requires content. Another is expensive and doesn’t have a user-friendly interface nor user friendly support staff, but fulfills its functional role really well.</p>,<p>End of the day, we have various silo driven automated systems that find us prospective customers from various platforms and sends them emails, messages or texts about our products and services and somehow someone calls me to hire my team or one of our lead generation technologies for their sales or marketing programs.</p>,<p>“What else could I ask for?” I asked the CEO who was calling me. “Haven’t you heard the quote “If it isn’t broken, don’t fix it?” I said.</p>,<p>He listened and responded with:</p>,<ul><li>“are you exponentially increasing your revenues?” and</li><li>“are you working with companies we want to work with?”</li></ul>,<p>The truthful answer was no. I wasn’t.</p>,<p>So, I decided to give their artificial intelligence lead generation technology a try.</p>,<p>Now here comes the good part - I got 350 customized leads in less than 71 hours and 93% of them have instantly became qualified customers.</p>,<p>Given how fast artificial intelligence is being implemented in organizations, I’m thinking all organizations sooner or later will try artificial intelligence lead generation technologies.</p>,<p>So here are my 4 tips in how to get started:</p>,<p>1) Research artificial intelligence lead generation technologies. You should come up to 12 different platforms.</p>,<p>2) Price points vary from $199 month up to $5,700 for a pilot. Test 1-2 of these platforms in a campaign you’ve got going is worth it.</p>,<p>3) Onboarding time is a bit time consuming. Regardless of which platform you decide to use, machine learning requires input/guidance from you. So, unless you are working with lead generation consulting company like mine (The Access Group: www.access-group.ca), you have to put time aside in learning which platform to use and how to program the machine learning to provide you with instant (qualified) leads.</p>,<p>4) Regardless of how many different sales programs, sales campaigns or various lead generation technologies, services, etc. that you use, once you replace outdated data with “artificial intelligent data”, your entire lead generation system will be enhanced and the results you produce will dramatically increase. Said differently, if your sales quota is $1 million, be prepared to exceed it and hit a $3 million goal.</p>,<p>Now here comes the good part: You will no longer have to work with junk leads. Your sales cycles will reduce from 8 months down to something that is much less – for me, it got down to 71 hours. This instantly reduces the cost of sale. For me, I don’t have to pay my sales staff (as an example) salaries for 8 months before I get a return on investment. I can get it much faster.</p>,<p>What you need to keep in mind is that Artificial Intelligence is not a</p>,<ul><li>CRM system</li><li>Predictable analytics software solution</li><li>An email system</li><li>A complicated system that no one will use or have time for</li></ul>,<p>Artificial Intelligence is an intelligence technology that will tell you (and your sales force) who to contact, and their contact information.</p>,<p>So back to the question my vendor asked me…</p>,<p>Am I exponentially growing my business? The truth is that I don’t know. I certainly say my pipeline is full and I’m consistently increasing my prices.</p>,<p>Am I working with companies that I want to work with - and the answer for me is “absolutely”!</p>,<p>Sincerely,</p>,<p>Taimour Zaman</p>,<p>p.s. I hope you found my content helpful. If you would like some help in identifying a technology that is right for you and your organization, please feel free to book a complimentary blue print call with me here: <a href="https://live.vcita.com/site/taimourzaman">https://live.vcita.com/site/taimourzaman</a></p>]]></description>
            <link>http://accessgroup.help/blog/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f6b1ff71-ca44-4d2b-951d-eb3dc14da6b6</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 21:23:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Contact Us]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Contact Us</h1>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-location/?latitude=43.735389&longitude=-79.348046&zoom=16&address=170%20The%20Donway%20W%2C%20Toronto%2C%20Ontario%20M3C%202G3%2C%20Canada"></iframe>,<p>The Access Group: 6A – 170 Donway West Suite 1403, M3C2E8</p>,<p>(416)489-9541</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://accessgroup.help/contact-us/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c7f8ccbc-8e93-4d5e-8b4e-78decc993775</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2017 21:23:26 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>